And Coco Gauff continues to refuse to lose
科科 高芙仍保持不败
before the semifinals in Beijing.
在北京的半决赛之前
北京时间10月5号夜场 中网第三轮
16岁的孙心然
第一次参加巡回赛正赛
已经连赢两场 现在
她面对世界第4高芙
先看首盘2比2这一局
孙心然连续从底线抽击
扛住高芙的回球 最后保发 3比2
Dip below sixty degrees Fahrenheit,
气温降到华氏六十度以下
low teens Celsius.
也就是摄氏十几度
Quality stuff from the youngster.
这位小将打得真漂亮
下一局 高芙把球打得更深
孙心然退到底线后 仍然继续抽击
看她怎样把这一分争回来
She just continues to bash the ball.
她还在不断大力击球
I mean, just continue to watch.
我是说 继续看下去
And Sun is back on the lettering on the court.
孙心然又退到场上字母标志处
But here, it’s all right in front of her.
而现在 机会就在她眼前
孙心然随后5比4领先
但那是高芙的发球局
不是孙心然拿到了盘点
高芙追平 再拿下孙心然的发球局
6比5
And Coco Gauff back out in front
科科 高芙再度领先
for the first time in forty minutes,
这是四十分钟来的第一次
and she’s got triple set point.
她拿到了三个盘点
And it’s a swing and a miss.
这一拍挥空了
And that’s a little deflated look.
她的神情有些低落
The shoulders have fallen for Sun Xinran,
孙心然垂下了肩膀
because Coco Gauff finds a way to earn the opening set.
因为科科 高芙设法拿下首盘
It wasn’t easy, but she gets it done
并不容易 但她还是拿下首盘
in just short of an hour.
用时不到一小时
第二盘 高芙先拿两局
孙心然的发球局里 还在拉锯
高芙的第三个破发点来了
高芙从首盘4比5
连赢6局 第二盘3比0
孙心然仍拿下对手一个发球局
追到1比3 之后
高芙再连赢3局结束比赛
一发赢分 两人都是33分拿20
二发才拉开 孙心然32分拿八分
高芙22分拿14分
她还有可以补上的地方
孙心然以5比7 1比6告负
但第一次巡回赛正赛 已连赢两场
高芙赛后说
她比自己16岁时更成熟
也期待以后再交手
遗憾之后 未来可期
下一次 她会带来怎样的惊喜？
Coco, relentless.
科科毫不松懈
She loves the middle of the court today.
今天她很喜欢利用场地中路
And Coco Gauff continues to refuse to lose
科科 高芙仍保持不败
before the semifinals in Beijing.
在北京的半决赛之前
Well, on paper
从纸面实力看
it looked like it was going to be a beatdown.
本该是一场悬殊的较量
Number four in the world
世界第四
versus five eighty-two.
对阵世界第五百八十二
The opening set was more competitive
首盘的激烈程度
than anyone could have imagined.
超出了所有人的想象
But in the end, it’s Coco Gauff
但最终 是科科 高芙
who strikes a commanding pose
展现出了压倒性的优势
in the second set,
在第二盘
as she runs away with it.
一路拉开了差距
And now she finds her way to the round of sixteen
现在她晋级十六强
at this WTA one thousand event
在这站 WTA 一千赛
with a seven-five, six-one win.
以七比五 六比一获胜